<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Foodie</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="terms_and_conditions">
        Welcome to [App Name]! Please read these terms and conditions carefully before using our services.\n\n
    1. Acceptance of Terms\n
    By using our app, you agree to these Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree, please do not use the app.\n\n
    2. Eligibility\n
    You must be at least 18 years old to create an account and use our services. By creating an account, you confirm that you meet this age requirement.\n\n
    3. User Responsibilities\n
    - Provide accurate and up-to-date information during registration.\n
    - Keep your account credentials secure and confidential.\n
    - Notify us immediately if you suspect unauthorized use of your account.\n\n
    4. Order Placement and Cancellation\n
    - Orders placed through the app are subject to acceptance by the restaurant.\n
    - Cancellation policies may vary depending on the restaurant\'s terms.\n
    - Refunds for canceled orders will follow the refund policy specified in the app.\n\n
    5. Delivery Terms\n
    - Delivery times are estimates and may vary due to unforeseen circumstances.\n
    - Ensure someone is available to receive the order at the provided delivery address.\n\n
    6. Payment\n
    - All payments must be made through the app using the available payment methods.\n
    - Prices are subject to change without prior notice.\n\n
    7. Intellectual Property\n
    All content in the app, including text, graphics, logos, and images, is the property of [App Name] and is protected by copyright laws.\n\n
    8. Liability Limitation\n
    We are not responsible for:\n
    - Delays or failures in delivery caused by third parties.\n
    - Food quality or hygiene issues.\n
    - Losses arising from unauthorized account access.\n\n
    9. Changes to Terms\n
    We reserve the right to modify these terms at any time. Updates will be posted in the app, and continued use of the app constitutes acceptance of the updated terms.\n\n
    10. Contact Us\n
    If you have any questions about these Terms and Conditions, please contact us at support@[yourappdomain].com.
</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy">
    Your privacy is important to us. Please read our Privacy Policy carefully to understand how we collect, use, and protect your personal information.\n\n
    1. Information We Collect\n
    - Personal information such as name, email address, and phone number.\n
    - Payment details for order processing.\n
    - Location data for delivery purposes.\n
    - Usage data such as app interactions and preferences.\n\n
    2. How We Use Your Information\n
    - To process your orders and provide delivery services.\n
    - To improve our app functionality and user experience.\n
    - To send promotional offers, updates, and notifications.\n
    - To comply with legal obligations and prevent fraud.\n\n
    3. Sharing of Information\n
    - We may share your information with trusted third-party partners, such as delivery personnel and payment processors.\n
    - Your data will not be sold or shared with unauthorized parties.\n\n
    4. Data Security\n
    - We implement advanced security measures to protect your data.\n
    - However, no method of transmission over the Internet is completely secure, and we cannot guarantee absolute security.\n\n
    5. Your Rights\n
    - You can access, update, or delete your personal information by contacting us.\n
    - You can opt-out of receiving promotional messages at any time.\n\n
    6. Changes to This Policy\n
    - We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time.\n
    - Continued use of the app constitutes acceptance of the updated policy.\n\n
    7. Contact Us\n
    If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at support@[yourappdomain].com.
</string>

</resources>